As new technology is introduced, there are many who worry about its impact on our current and future lifestyles – particularly when it comes to jobs.
随着新技术的引入，很多人担心它对我们当前和未来生活方式的影响——尤其是在工作方面。
It is a current belief that with the rise of robotics and artificial intelligence, many people’s jobs, and therefore their livelihoods, are likely to be lost to automation.
目前人们普遍认为，随着机器人技术和人工智能的兴起，许多人的工作，进而他们的生计，可能会因自动化（automation）而丧失。
This type of fear isn’t new.
这种担忧并非新鲜事。
In the 19th century, the automated weaving machine was revolutionising the English textiles industry and would contribute to the Industrial Revolution.
在19世纪，自动织布机彻底改变了英国的纺织业，并促成了工业革命。
When manual workers became redundant, it sparked protests at the loss of their vocation.
当手工工人被裁员（redundant）时，就引发了人们对失去工作（vocation）的抗议。
Automation in the work place is nothing new.
工作场所的自动化并非新鲜事物。
Machines have been performing menial tasks on our behalf for years, allowing us to escape the drudgery that accompanies many repetitive jobs.
多年来，机器一直在替我们执行枯燥琐碎的（menial）任务，使我们得以摆脱许多重复性工作所带来的辛苦乏味的苦差事；单调乏味（drudgery）。
In fact, the International Federation of Robotics states that in manufacturing on average there are now 74 robots per 10,000 employees.
事实上，国际机器人联合会指出，在制造业中，目前平均每10000名员工就有74台机器人。
That has risen from 66 in 2015.
这一数字与2015年66台相比有所上升。
General Manager of Digital Customer Engagement Solutions at tech firm Nuance, Bernard Louvat, believes that ‘AI is a big threat to low-skilled jobs, no question.’
科技公司Nuance的数字客户互动解决方案总经理伯纳德・卢瓦特（Bernard Louvat）认为，“毫无疑问，人工智能对低技能工作来说是一个巨大威胁。”
He also thinks that AI chatbots will oust most call centre staff within a decade.
他还认为，人工智能聊天机器人将在十年内取代（oust）大多数呼叫中心员工。
When you consider that a large telecoms company like AT&T employs around 100,000 call centre staff, that’s a lot of people on the dole.
当你想到像美国电话电报公司（AT&T）这样的大型电信公司雇佣了约10万名呼叫中心员工时，那就意味着会有很多人靠失业救济金生活。
And that’s just one industry.
而这只是一个行业。
A recent report from the McKinsey Global Institute, a private sector think tank, states that nearly two thirds of all jobs could have at least 30% of their activities automated by 2030.
私营企业智库麦肯锡全球研究所（McKinsey Global Institute）最近的一份报告指出，到2030年，几乎三分之二的工作至少有30%的工作内容可以实现自动化。
However, McKinsey also believes that this new technology will also ‘create new occupations that do not exist today, much as technologies in the past have done.’
然而，麦肯锡也认为，这项新技术也会“创造出如今尚不存在的新职业，就像过去的技术所做的那样”。
As the horse gave way to the car, hostlers became mechanics and mechanised manufacturing drove up wages and created more long-term roles than it destroyed.
随着马被汽车取代，马夫（hostlers）变成了机械师，机械化制造业提高了工资水平，创造出的长期岗位比它淘汰的岗位更多。
In fact, figures from the World Bank have shown that despite a 2.2 billion rise in population between 1991 and 2017, global unemployment has fallen by 0.3%.
事实上，世界银行的数据显示，尽管1991年至2017年间人口增加了22亿，但全球失业率却下降了0.3%。
‘It’s an evolution of work’ says Ian Barkin, co-founder of Symphony Ventures, a robotic process automation specialist.
Symphony Ventures的联合创始人，机器人流程自动化专家伊恩・巴金（Ian Barkin）说：“这是工作的一种进化。”
As low-skilled jobs are taken on by AI, people will need to learn new skills.
随着人工智能承担低技能工作，人们将需要学习新技能。
‘This calls on us to focus on up-skilling, Technology can lead to job reductions but it doesn’t have to,’ says Barkin.
巴金说：“这就要求我们专注于技能提升（up-skilling）。技术可能会导致工作岗位减少，但也并非必然如此。”
Whether or not robotics and AI will leave us all jobless remains to be seen.
机器人技术和人工智能是否会让我们都失业还有待观察。
Current views on the subject are mixed.
目前关于这个问题的观点不一。
Increased automation could indeed lead to a loss of some jobs, but at the same time is likely to create many more as new skills are required.
自动化程度的提高确实可能导致一些工作岗位的流失，但同时，由于需要新技能，也可能会创造出更多的岗位。
Will they balance out?
它们会达到平衡吗？
I’ll get my AI assistant to get back to you on that one.
关于这一点，我会让我的人工智能助手再回复你。